{
    "subject": "resource/Kingdom_of_Asturias",
    "predicate": "ontology/capital",
    "object": "resource/Oviedo",
    "human_readable": "The capital of Kingdom of Asturias is Oviedo.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9177865982055664,
            "question": "Is Oviedo the capital city of a kingdom?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8983163833618164,
            "question": "What kingdom has Oviedo as its capital?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8801785111427307,
            "question": "What is the capital of the Kingdom of Asturias?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.578937292098999,
            "question": "Name a country that contains the Kingdom of Asturias."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5425838828086853,
            "question": "What is another name for the Kingdom of Asturias?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5070119500160217,
            "question": "Where is Oviedo located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4208550453186035,
            "question": "What historical events have shaped Oviedo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2862088084220886,
            "question": "What is the significance of Oviedo in Spanish history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2781746983528137,
            "question": "What are some key features of Oviedo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.257535845041275,
            "question": "How has Oviedo developed over time?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The capital of Kingdom of Asturias is Oviedo.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8861_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some key features of Oviedo?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8861_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of Oviedo in Spanish history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8861_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What historical events have shaped Oviedo?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8861_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8861_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8861_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8861_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8861_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8861_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8861_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8861_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8861_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8861_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8861_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. According to document #49 (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8861/re-ranker-msmarco/49.txt), The Kingdom of Asturias was a kingdom in the Iberian Peninsula that existed from 718 to 910, with Oviedo serving as its capital."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided documents consistently mention that Oviedo served as the capital of the Kingdom of Asturias, supporting the statement that \"The capital of Kingdom of Asturias is Oviedo.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}